Panu Robert Niskakoski

Technical Game Artist & Generalist

★ CONTACT

- Finland, Jyväskylä
- paroni.does@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn
- Online Portfolio
- My Website

Ö

DEV TOOLS



Procreate & Gimp

Unity & GMS

Blender

Aseprite

Reaper & Audacity

Trello & Asana

Vegas Studio Pro

Github Desktop

PROGRAMMING

C#

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

Java

LANGUAGES



Finnish

English

Swedish

REFERENCES



EDUCATION

→ MASTER OF SCIENCE (IT) **→**

University of Jyväskylä | 2017 – 2022

Masters thesis about animal-computer interaction (ACI)

♦ NCO-Course ◆

Karjala Brigade | 2013 - 2014

•

ABOUT ME



I have worked on commercial projects for 5 years as an entrepreneur in the game industry. I have a versatile skill set in creating 3D / 2D graphics & animation, game design, sound production (SFX / MUSIC) as well as game programming.

I have a master's degree in IT from the University of Jyväskylä. In my studies, I focused on game design and development.

I've done freelance graphic design gigs varying from band shirts to deck designs and from company logos to social media creatives.

듵

WORK EXPERIENCE



★ CEO & LEAD DESIGNER ★

Herra Koira Company | 2023 – present

Game design – Research - Graphics & Animation - Sound design

Marketing material – Prototyping - QA

★ GAME ARTIST & GENERALIST ★

Unibyte Studios | 2019 – 2023 2D Graphics - Marketing material - Music & SFX – Testing - Design

★ GRAPHIC DESIGNER ★

Freelance | 2018 – present

3D modeling - Company logos - Shirt designs - Social media creatives
Prints - Business charts - Skateboard decks

★ DEPARTMENT MANAGER ★

K-Supermarket Kotikenttä | 2014 – 2017

Orders - Campaigns - Loss tracking – Inventory – Sales negotiations









Will be given upon request.